<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Supervised Learning on In Code We Trust</title>
    <link>/categories/supervised-learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Supervised Learning on In Code We Trust</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/supervised-learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My Heart Will Go Down</title>
      <link>/2018/11/my-heart-will-go-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/11/my-heart-will-go-down/</guid>
      <description>The sinking of the RMS Titanic on April 15, 1912 after colliding with an iceberg during her maiden voyage from Southampton to New York City, is one of the most infamous shipwrecks in history. It is one of the deadliest commercial peacetime maritime disasters in modern history, killing 1502 out of 2224 passengers and crew and this sensational tragedy shocked the international community. Both Thomas Andrews, her architect, and Capt. Edward Smith, who was in command, went down with the ship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Eat, or not to Eat, that is the Question</title>
      <link>/2018/03/to-eat-or-not-to-eat-that-is-the-question/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/03/to-eat-or-not-to-eat-that-is-the-question/</guid>
      <description>Mycology is the branch of biology concerned with the study of fungi, including their genetic and biochemical properties, their taxonomy and their use to humans as a source for tinder, medicine, food, and entheogens, as well as their dangers, such as toxicity or infection. It’s complicated and fascinating at the same time.
I wasn’t particularly fond of it at the university.
On the other hand I really enjoy eating mushroom. I normally buy them at the local market, so safety is no real concern of mine.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>